{"showBridgeTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/61941/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":61941,"taskName":"Sink Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Install or Repair a Sink","xmTaskDescriptor":"Kitchen \u0026 Bathroom Sink Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":221,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"sink, faucet, under-mount, top-mount, farmhouse","textMessagingName":"Sink","rolloverLongDesc":"How the sink is mounted on the counter top (top-mount, under-mount, apron, basin) will determine what the opening in the counter top needs to be.","rolloverShortDesc":"Installing or repairing any type of sink","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Repair a Sink.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Sink Repair \u0026 Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Sink Replacement","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":60,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Sink Install or Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Sink - Repair or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Sink Project","urlName":"Sink-Install-or-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Sink Repair \u0026 Installation Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"sink, bathroom, plumber, laundry, kitchen, wet bar plumbing, plumbers, drip, leak, vanity, spigot, valve, faucet, farmhouse","emcCategoryOid":-12058,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8345,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"taskHeader":"Kitchen \u0026 Bathroom Sink Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/61941/":{"taskOID":61941,"originalTaskOID":61941,"setID":8345,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502567,"questionDisplayText":"What material is your sink made of?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What material is your sink made of?","shortQuestionText":"What material is your sink made of?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203470,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Enameled Cast Iron","answerDisplayText":"Enameled Cast Iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203471,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Granite Composite","answerDisplayText":"Granite Composite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Marble","answerDisplayText":"Marble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4717,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Plastic","answerDisplayText":"Plastic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203472,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Porcelain","answerDisplayText":"Porcelain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6016,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Stainless Steel","answerDisplayText":"Stainless Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502568,"questionDisplayText":"Where is the sink located?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the sink located?","shortQuestionText":"Where is the sink located?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203473,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom sink","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203474,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen sink","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203475,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Laundry room sink","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203476,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outdoor sink","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502569,"questionDisplayText":"How is the sink mounted?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How is the sink mounted?","shortQuestionText":"How is the sink mounted?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203477,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Apron (farmhouse)","answerDisplayText":"Apron (farmhouse)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203478,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Free standing","answerDisplayText":"Free standing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203479,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Top-mounted","answerDisplayText":"Top-mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203480,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Under-mounted","answerDisplayText":"Under-mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203481,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Vessel","answerDisplayText":"Vessel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203482,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall mounted","answerDisplayText":"Wall mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502567,"questionDisplayText":"What material is your sink made of?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What material is your sink made of?","shortQuestionText":"What material is your sink made of?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203470,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Enameled Cast Iron","answerDisplayText":"Enameled Cast Iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203471,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Granite Composite","answerDisplayText":"Granite Composite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Marble","answerDisplayText":"Marble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4717,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Plastic","answerDisplayText":"Plastic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203472,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Porcelain","answerDisplayText":"Porcelain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6016,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Stainless Steel","answerDisplayText":"Stainless Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203470,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Enameled Cast Iron","answerDisplayText":"Enameled Cast Iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203471,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Granite Composite","answerDisplayText":"Granite Composite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Marble","answerDisplayText":"Marble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4717,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Plastic","answerDisplayText":"Plastic","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203472,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Porcelain","answerDisplayText":"Porcelain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6016,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Stainless Steel","answerDisplayText":"Stainless Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502568,"questionDisplayText":"Where is the sink located?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the sink located?","shortQuestionText":"Where is the sink located?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203473,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom sink","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203474,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen sink","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203475,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Laundry room sink","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203476,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outdoor sink","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203473,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bathroom sink","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203474,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Kitchen sink","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203475,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Laundry room sink","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203476,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outdoor sink","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor sink","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502569,"questionDisplayText":"How is the sink mounted?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How is the sink mounted?","shortQuestionText":"How is the sink mounted?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203477,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Apron (farmhouse)","answerDisplayText":"Apron (farmhouse)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203478,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Free standing","answerDisplayText":"Free standing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203479,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Top-mounted","answerDisplayText":"Top-mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203480,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Under-mounted","answerDisplayText":"Under-mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203481,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Vessel","answerDisplayText":"Vessel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203482,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall mounted","answerDisplayText":"Wall mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203477,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Apron (farmhouse)","answerDisplayText":"Apron (farmhouse)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203478,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Free standing","answerDisplayText":"Free standing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203479,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Top-mounted","answerDisplayText":"Top-mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203480,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Under-mounted","answerDisplayText":"Under-mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203481,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Vessel","answerDisplayText":"Vessel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203482,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall mounted","answerDisplayText":"Wall mounted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}